邪恶力量前情提要
Previously on Supernatural.
跟你弟弟说晚安
Let's say good night to your brother.
晚安 萨姆
Good night, Sam.
嘿 迪恩
Hey, Dean.
爸爸
Daddy!
嘿 小家伙
Hey, buddy.
好梦 萨姆
Sweet dreams, Sam.
爸爸失踪了
Dad's missing.
我需要你来帮我找到他
Help me find him.
找寻爸爸的希望
The trail for Dad.
一天比一天渺茫
it's getting colder every day.
你认为我不像你那么想找到爸爸？
l wanna find Dad as much as you do.
妈妈死了 她再也回不来了
Mom's gone, and she isn't coming back.
不许你这么说她
Don't talk about her like that.
（劳伦斯 堪萨斯）
妈妈
Mommy?
嘿 甜心
Hey, sweetie.
为什么不去睡觉？
Why aren't you in bed?
我的衣柜里有东西
There's something in my closet.
看 什么都没有
See? There's nothing there.
你确定？
You're sure?
我确定
l'm sure.
来 睡觉吧
Now, come on. Into bed.
我不喜欢这栋房子
I don't like this house.
你只是现在还没习惯
You're just not used to it yet.
但你和你弟弟还有我
But you and your brother and me.
我们住在这会很幸福的
we are going to be very happy here.
我发誓
I promise.
我爱你
I love you.
椅子
The chair.
好吧
Okay. Right.
椅子
The chair.
为了安全
Just to be safe.
天啊 千万别是老鼠
Please, God, don't let it be rats.
好恐怖
Terrific.
《邪恶力量》
好的 我在浏览一些网站
All right. I've been cruising some websites.
想找到侯选的下一站目的地
I think I found a few candidates for our next gig.
在卡利海岸找到了一首捕鱼船
A fishing trawler found off the coast of Cali, its crew vanished.
它的船员都消失了 在西边的船仓里发现有破坏的痕迹
And we've got some cattle mutilations in West Texas.
嘿 我说这些猎鬼的事很无聊吗？
Hey! Am I boring you with this hunting-evil stuff?
不 我在听
No. I'm listening.
继续
Keep going.
有个萨克啦曼多人用枪射击自己头
And here, a Sacramento man shot himself in the head.
三次
Three times.
你对这些没一点想法 兄弟？
Any of these things blowing up your skirt, pal?
- 我以前见过这个 - 见过什么？
- Wait, l've seen this. - Seen what?
你在干吗？
What are you doing?
迪恩 我知道下一站去哪呢
Dean, I know where we have to go next.
哪儿？
Where?
回家
Back home.
回堪萨斯
Back to Kansas.
好 随你
Okay, random.
为什么那么想？
Where did that come from?
这张照片是在我们家门前拍的 对吗？
All right, this photo was taken in front of our old house, right?
- 妈妈死的那所房子？- 是的
- The house where Mom died? - Yeah.
它被火烧塌了 可没完全毁了 他们重建了它 对吗？
It didn't burn down, not completely. They rebuilt it, right?
我想是的
I guess so.
你究竟想说什么？
What are you talking about?
听着 这也许听起来很疯狂
Okay, look. This is gonna sound crazy…
但现在住在我们老房子里的人
but the people who live in our old house…
我觉得他们处境危险
l think they might be in danger.
你为什么那么想？
Why would you think that?
听着 你得相信我 好吗？
st Look, just You gotta trust me on this, okay?
相信你？
Okay, whoa, whoa. Trust you?
- 是的 - 那不行 你得给我个其它的理由
- Yeah. - You gotta give me a little more than that.
我真的不能解释
l can't really explain it is all.
好啊
Well, tough.
你不说理由 我哪也不去
I'm not going anywhere until you do.
我会做噩梦
I have these nightmares.
这我知道
I've noticed.
有时它们会实现
And sometimes they come true.
又是那个梦？
Come again?
听着 迪恩
Look, Dean…
在杰西卡死前很多天前我就梦到过
l dreamt about Jessica's death for days before it happened.
正常人都会做奇怪的梦 伙计
Sam, people have weird dreams, man.
我觉得那是巧合
I'm sure it's just a coincidence.
不 我梦到血滴下来 她在天花板上 那火焰
No I dreamt about the blood, her on the ceiling, the fire.
因为我不相信 所以我什么都没做
I didn't do anything because I didn't believe it.
现在我梦到了那棵树 我们的房子
Now I'm dreaming about that tree, our house…
里面尖叫着救命的女人
and about some woman screaming for help.
这又开始了
That's where it all started, man.
这一定意味着什么 对吗？
This has to mean something, right?
我不知道
I don't know.
你什么意思啊 迪恩？
What do you mean, you don't know?
这个女人可能处境很危险
This woman might be in danger.
也许就是这个怪物杀了妈妈和杰西卡
This might be the thing that killed Mom.
打住 好吗？
All right. Just slow down, would you?
首先你说 你得到暗示
I mean, first you tell me you've got the Shining…
然后你就要我和你一起回家
and then you tell me that I've gotta go back home.
特别是当我
Especially when…
当什么？
When what?
当我发誓再也不回那里
When I swore to myself that I would never go back there.
迪恩 我们必须要查清楚
Look…Dean, we have to check this out.
去确认这些
Just to make sure.
我知道 我们去
I know we do.
你还好吧 伙计？
You gonna be all right, man?
我跟着你进去
Let me get back to you on that.
你是？
Yes?
很抱歉打搅到你 女士 我们是政府…
Sorry to bother you, madam. We're with the.
我是 萨姆·温彻斯特 这是我哥迪恩
l'm Sam Winchester. And this is my brother, Dean.
我们以前住这
We used to live here.
我们刚好路过
You know, we were just driving by…
我们想是否能看看这老房子
and we were wondering if we could come see the old place.
这太有趣了
Winchester.
昨天晚上
Yeah, that's so funny.
我刚好找到些你们的照片
You know I think I found some of your photos the other night.
真的？
You did?
好的 请进
Okay. Come on in.
果汁 果汁 果汁
Juice. Juice. Juice.
那是里奇 他就喜欢喝果汁
That's Richie. He's kind of a juice junkie.
但他其实挺懂礼貌的
But, hey, at least he won't get scurvy.
莎丽 这是 萨姆和迪恩
Sari, this is Sam and Dean.
他们以前住在这里
They used to live here.
- 嗨 - 嗨 莎丽
- Hi. - Hey, Sari.
你刚搬进来？
So you just moved in?
是的 从威其塔
Yeah. From Wichita.
你在这有亲戚？
You got family here, or…?
不 我只是 需要一个新的开始
No, I just…needed a fresh start.
就是那样
that's all.
所以新镇子 新工作 我找到这新房子
new town, new job I mean, as soon as I find one. New house.
你觉得这里怎么样？
So how you liking it so far?
我很尊重你们童年的这栋房子
Well, all due respect to your childhood home.
你们一定在这里度过了不少快乐时光
I mean, l'm sure you have lots of happy memories here.
但这房子有问题
but this place has its issues.
你什么意思？
What do you mean?
它有点老了
Well, it's just getting old.
比如房子里的配线 你也清楚？
Like the wiring, you know?
我这里灯常常一闪闪的
We've got flickering lights almost hourly.
哦 这可不太好
That's too bad.
还有什么？
What else?
水槽常堵死
Sink's backed up.
地下室还有老鼠
There's rats in the basement.
我很抱歉
l'm sorry.
我不是想抱怨
I don't mean to complain.
不 你是见到了老鼠 还是只听到刮刻的声音？
No.Have you seen the rats or have you just heard scratching?
实际上只是声音
It's just the scratching, actually.
妈妈
Mom?
问问他们 他们在这住的时候 它就在这里了吗？
Ask them if it was here when they lived here.
什么 莎丽？
What, Sari?
我衣柜里的东西
The thing in my closet.
不 宝贝 衣柜里什么都没有
Oh, no, baby. There was nothing in their closets.
对吗？
Right?
对的 是
Right.
是的 当然什么都没有
No, no, of course not.
几天前的夜里她做过噩梦
She had a nightmare the other night.
不是做梦 它走到了我的卧室里 身上是火焰
l wasn't dreaming. It came into my bedroom, and it was on fire.
- 一个全身带火的影像 - 詹妮是你梦里的那个女人？
- You hear that? A figure on fire. - That was the woman in your dreams?
对 你也听到她说什么了
Yeah.She was talking about scratching.
刮刻的声音 闪烁的灯光？
flickering lights.
都是恶鬼存在的迹象
Both signs of a malevolent spirit.
我才意识到你的奇怪的梦正在实现
I'm just freaked out your weirdo visions are coming true.Forget.
那屋子里的东西 你不觉得就是它杀了妈妈和杰西卡？
that a minute. The thing in the house, think it killed Mom?
我不知道
l don't know.
它是回来了还是它一直都在那里？
Has it come back? Has it been there the whole time?
也许完全是其它的东西呢 我们一点也不清楚 萨姆
Or it's something else entirely.
那些人很危险
Well, those people are in danger, Dean.
我们得帮他们离开那房子
We have to get them out.
我们以后会
And we will.
不 我是说现在
No, I mean now.
那怎么做？她会相信你的故事？
How you gonna do that? Got a story she'll believe?
那我们该怎么做？
What are we supposed to do?
我们必须得冷静 必须这样
We just gotta chill out, that's all.
如果是其它的情况下 我们会怎么做？
If this was any other kind ofjob, what would we do?
我们得查清楚我们面对的是什么
We'd try to figure out what we were dealing with.
我们要研究这房子的历史
We'd dig into the history of the house.
对 除了我们知道的东西外的情况
Except we already know what happened.
可我们知道多少？
Yeah, but how much do we know?
你还记得多少？
How much do you actually remember?
你是说哪天晚上吗？
About that night, you mean?
是的 记得不是太多
Yeah. Not much.
我记得那火焰 热浪
I remember the fire. The heat.
我抱着你从前门逃出来
Then I carried you out the front door.
你做的？
You did?
是的 你不知道？
Yeah. Why, you never knew that?
不知道
No.
你和我一样也知道爸爸的事 妈妈她…
And, well, you know Dad's story as well as I do. Mom was…
就在天花板上
Was on the ceiling.
爸爸发现她的时候 那个把她钉在那的东西早走了
Whatever put her there was long gone by the time Dad found her.
他一点也不知道那究竟是怎么回事吗？
And he never had a theory about what did it?
如果他知道 那就是他不愿意透露
If he did, he kept it to himself.
老天也知道我问了他多少次
God knows we asked him enough times.
好的
Okay.
看来我们要弄清楚现在是什么
So if we're gonna figure out what's going on now…
我们得查出原来的情况
we have to figure out what happened back then…
看看它是不是同一个东西
and see if it's the same thing.
对
Yeah.
和爸的朋友邻居 住在这的人都谈谈
Talk to Dad's friends, neighbors. People who were there at the time.
这对你又是个难题吧？
Does this feel like just another job to you?
我马上回来 我去下厕所
I'll be right back. I gotta go the bathroom.
我是约翰·温彻斯特
This is John Winchester.
如果情况紧急 请打给我的儿子迪恩 866- 907- 3235
If this is an emergency, call my son, Dean. 866-907-3235.
爸爸
Dad…
我以前留过信息
l know l've left you messages before.
我不知道你收到了没
I don't even know if you get them.
但我现在和萨姆一起
But l'm with Sam…
我们在劳伦斯
and we're in Lawrence…
我们家的老房子里有东西
and there's something in our old house.
我不清楚那是不是杀害妈妈的凶手
I don't know if it's the thing that killed Mom or not…
但是
but…
我不知道该怎么做
l don't know what to do.
无论你现在在做什么 如果你能来这里
So whatever you're doing, if you could get here…
求你了 我需要你的帮助 爸爸
Please. I need your help, Dad.
不 长官 这里没有什么古怪 我发誓
No, sir. Nothing weird down there, I promise.
水槽堵住了而已
Sink just backed up on its own.
让我看看
Well, l'll take a look.
谢谢
Thanks.
那我不挡着你干活了
Oh, okay. l'll get out of your way.
你和约翰·温彻斯特以前一起拥有这个车厂？
So you and John Winchester, you used to own this garage together?
是的 好久前的事了
Yeah, we used to. A long time ago.
事实上约翰失踪大概20年了
Matter of fact, it must be 20 years since John disappeared.
为什么现在警察突然对这很感兴趣？
So why are the cops interested?
我们在重新调查一些未解决的案子
We're reopening some unsolved cases.
其中一个案子就是温彻斯特失踪
and the Winchester disappearance is one.
好吧 你想知道关于约翰的什么？
ell, what do you wanna know? Whatever you remember.
你记得的全部 全都告诉我们
Whatever sticks out in your mind.
他相当顽固 我还记得
He was a stubborn bastard, I remember that.
无论做什么他都想赢 你知道吗？
And whatever the game, he hated to lose, you know?
退役的军官的习惯
It was the whole Marine thing.
但 他深爱着玛丽
But he sure loved Mary.
对他的孩子们也是
And he doted on those kids.
可这是大火以前的事
But that was before the fire?
是的。-
That's right.
他有没有说过那场大火？
He ever talk about that night?
不 刚开始一点也不提
No. Not at first.
我觉得那时他太悲痛了
think he was in shock. Right.
对 但后来他
But eventually?
他说了些什么？
What did he say about it?
他开始有些古怪的想法
He wasn't thinking straight. He said…
他说有东西杀了玛丽放了那场大火
He said something caused that fire and killed Mary.
他说过是谁吗？
He ever say what did it?
没人那么做
Nothing did it.
那只是场事故
It was an accident.
天花板或墙里的电线短路或什么的
An electrical short in the ceiling or walls or something.
我叫他去见见心理医生 但
l begged him to get some help.
但怎么？
t… But what?
情况越来越糟糕
He just got worse and worse.
怎么啦？他开始阅读那些奇怪的古书
ow? Oh, he started reading these strange old books.
而且开始去见镇上那个看掌相的人
He started going to see this palm reader in town.
看掌相的人？
Palm-reader?
你知道名字吗？
Do you have a name?
不知道
No.
镇上还真有些通灵师和看掌相的人
So there are a few psychics and palm-readers in town.
有人叫做艾德唯罗
There's someone named El Divino.
还有神秘的佛特斯基先生
There's the mysterious Mr. Fortensky.
密苏里·莫斯利 还有些家伙
Issouri Mosley. Some dude named.
等等
Wait, wait.
密苏里·莫斯利？
Missouri Mosley?
怎么？
What?
是通灵师吗？
That's a psychic?
是的 我想是
Yeah. Yeah, I guess so.
在爸爸的日记里
Dad's journal.
来 看看这个
Come here. Look at this.
第一页 第一句话 读读看
First page, first sentence. Read that.
「我去密苏里那里」 「知道了真相」
"I went to Missouri and I learned the truth."
我原来还以为他是去了密苏里州
I always thought he meant the state.
好的 现在
All right, then.
你别担心了
Don't you worry about a thing.
- 你老婆对你很在乎的 - 好的 谢谢
- Your wife is crazy about you. - Well, thank you.
可怜的家伙 他老婆和园丁有一腿
r bastard. His woman is cold banging the gardener.
你为什么不告诉他呢？
Why didn't you tell him?
人们来这不是为了真相
People don't come here for the truth.
他们是来听好消息
They come for good news.
萨姆和迪恩 来吧 我今天可没什么时间
Well, Sam and Dean, come on already. I aingt got all day.
让我看看你
Well, let me look at you.
小家伙现在都是大帅哥了
You boys grew up handsome.
你那时候看起来真笨
And you were one goofy-looking kid too.
萨姆
Sam.
噢 亲爱的
Oh, honey.
你女朋友的事我很难过
I'm sorry about your girlfriend.
你爸爸
And your father.
他失踪了？
He's missing?
你怎么知道？
How did you know all that?
你们刚才就在想这些 就在刚才
Well… You were just thinking it, just now.
他在那里？他还好吗？
Where is he? Is he okay?
我也不知道
l don't know.
不知道？
Don't know?
可你是大师 对吗？
You're supposed to be a psychic, right?
孩子 你看到我拿骨头发功？
Boy, you see me sawing some bony tramp in half?
你以为我是巫婆吗？
You think I'm a magician?
我也许能读出人的想法感觉某些灵魂
I may read thoughts and sense energies in a room…
可我不能无中生有
but I can't just pull facts out of thin air.
请坐
Sit. Please.
你敢把臭脚摆在咖啡桌上的话
You put your foot on my coffee table,
我一定用勺子狠狠的扁你
I'm gonna whack you with a spoon.
我什么也没做啊
l didn't do anything.
可你刚才想那么做
You were thinking about it.
我们的爸爸
Okay. So our dad, when did you first meet him?
什么时候你第一次见他？
He came for a reading.
那场大火后 过了些日子他过来看书
A few days after the fire.
我只是告诉他 那东西的确来自黑暗
I just told him what was really out there in the dark.
我想你们会觉得是我把他带上这条猎魔之路
I guess you could say I drew back the curtains for him.
那火呢？
What about the fire?
你知道是什么杀了我们的妈妈吗？
Do you know about what killed our mom?
一点点
A little.
你爸爸和我说起过那房子
Your daddy took me to your house.
他希望我能去感应一下
He was hoping I could sense the echoes.
那东西的手印
the fingerprints of this thing.
你做到了？
And could you?
我不行
l don't…
那是什么？
What was it?
我不知道
l don't know.
哦…
Oh…
那一定是魔鬼
But it was evil.
对于那个人的手 我也很难过
uice. Juice. Juice. I feel awful about the poor man's hand.
可我为什么要负责任？
Wait, but how can I be held liable?
可我请不起律师
Yeah, but I can't afford a lawyer.
好 听着 我等会打回来
Okay, listen. You just gotta let me call you back.
里奇 妈妈等会就回来 好吗？
Richie, Mommy's gonna be right back, okay?
好的
kay. Okay.
你们认为有东西回到了那房子里？
So you think something's back in that house?
肯定是
Definitely.
我不知道
I don't understand.
为什么？
What?
我是没回去过了
I haven't been back inside…
可我对那里很注意 它很安静
but l've been keeping an eye on the place, and it's been quiet.
没有突然死亡 古怪的事故
No sudden deaths, no freak accidents.
为什么？
Why is it acting up now?
我也不知道
I don't know.
但爸爸失踪了 杰西卡也死了 这房子
But Dad going missing and Jessica dying and now this house.
都一起发生
all happening at once.
感觉像有事又开始了
it feels like something starting.
那可真让我鼓舞
That's a comforting thought.
果汁
Juice.
孩子 你老妈都快抓狂了
Oh, baby, either we have rats or Mommy is going crazy.
里奇
Richie?
Richie!
孩子 你在哪里？
Baby, where are you?
- 妈妈 - 哦 天啊
- Mama. - Oh, my God.
萨姆 迪恩
Sam, Dean.
你们来这里干吗？
What are you doing here?
嘿 詹妮
Hey, Jenny.
这是我们的朋友密苏里
This is our friend, Missouri.
如果不打搅的话 我想带她看看房子
We were hoping to show her the old house. You know.
想看看过去
for old times' sake.
你知道 现在不行
.You know what? This isn't a good time.
我有点忙
I'm kind of busy.
听着 詹妮 这很重要
Enny, it's important.
给这女孩一点空间 你没看到她很不安吗？
Give the poor girl a break. Can't you see she's upset?
原谅这个男孩
Forgive him.
他没恶意 他只是和人打交道脑子不好用
He means well. He's just not the sharpest tool in the shed.
但听我说
But hear me out.
- 关于什么？- 这房子
- About what? - About this house.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
你知道我在说什么
I think you know what I'm talking about.
你觉得这房子里有东西
You think there's something in this house.
它想伤害你的家人
Something that wants to hurt your family.
我说错了吗？
Am I mistaken?
你是谁？
Who are you?
我们是能帮忙的人 能阻止这一切
We're people who can help. Who can stop this thing.
但你得信任我们
But you're gonna have to trust us just a little.
如果这里有黑暗的力量
If there's a dark energy around here.
那么这个房间就是这力量的中心
this room should be the center of it.
为什么？
Why?
这就是你的婴儿房 萨姆
This used to be your nursery, Sam.
这是所有一切发生的地方
This is where it all happened.
电磁辐射器？「感应鬼魂的设备」
That an EMF?
是的
Yeah.
业余的人用的玩意
Amateur.
我不知道这是否让你们失望或松了口气
I don't know if you should be disappointed or relieved…
这不是杀害你妈妈的那个东西
but this aingt the thing that took your mom.
你确定？
Are you sure?
你怎么知道？
How do you know?
和我以前来这感觉到的力量不一样
It isn't the same energy I felt the last time I was here.
这不同
It's something different.
那是什么？
What is it?
不是它
Not it. Them.
是它们 这里不只一个灵魂
There's more than one spirit in this place.
他们在这里做什么？
What are they doing here?
他们因为你们的家人而聚集
They're here because of what happened to your family.
这些年来 鬼怪不停的在你身边出现
You see, all those years ago, real evil came to you.
它靠近这个房子
It walked this house.
那个魔鬼受了伤
That kind of evil leaves wounds.
伤口还感染了
And sometimes wounds get infected.
我不明白
I don't understand.
这地方对于超自然力量就像是「磁体」
This place is a magnet for paranormal energy.
它吸引了一个恶鬼
It's attracted a poltergeist.
一个很邪恶的东西
A nasty one.
詹妮和她的孩子没死 它不会罢休
And it won't rest until Jenny and her babies are dead.
你说这里不止一个灵魂
You said there was more than one spirit.
是的
There is.
我只是不太确定另一个是什么
I just can't quite make out the second one.
好吧 至少能确定一件事
Well, one thing's for damn sure.
我不会让别人再死在这里
Nobody's dying in this house ever again.
所以无论它是什么 我们怎么阻止它？
So whatever is here, how do we stop it?
这些材料是什么啊？
So, what is all this stuff, anyway?
当归根 大篷车的油 十字路口的尘土
Angelica Root, Van Van oil, crossroad dirt.
还有些其它材料
A few other odds and ends.
我们用这些干吗？
What are we supposed to do with it?
我们会在这房子的每层楼
We're gonna put them inside the walls…
的东南西北的墙里 放进这些东西
in the north, south, east, west corners on each floor of the house.
在墙上打洞 詹妮会「喜欢」我们这么做
We're gonna be punching holes in the drywall, Jenny's gonna love that.
可她会活着
She'll live.
这会摧毁那个鬼魂吗？
nd this will destroy the spirits? lt should.
当然 这房子从此就干净了
It should purify the house completely.
我们每人挑一层 但手脚得快点
'll each take a floor. But we work fast.
一旦鬼魂意识到我们在做什么 那时候就不太妙了
Once the spirits realize what we're up to things are gonna get bad.
好的
Okay.
小心
Careful.
你知道吗 把你们留在这里我不太放心
Look, l'm not sure I'm comfortable leaving you guys here alone.
带你的孩子去看电影或做点什么
Take your kids to the movie or something…
当你回来的时候什么都结束了
and it will be over by the time you get back.
好吧
Okay.
萨姆
Sam!
Sam.
你确定这都结束了？
You sure this is over?
我确定
I'm sure.
为什么？
Why?
为什么你这么问？
Why do you ask?
别介意
Never mind.
应该结束了 我也觉得
It's nothing, I guess.
你好？
Hello?
我们回来了
We're home.
发生了什么？
What happened?
嘿 对不起 我们会赔偿这一切
Hi. Sorry. We'll pay for all of this.
别担心
Don't you worry.
迪恩会收拾残局的
Dean's gonna clean up this mess.
你还傻在这干吗 孩子？
Well, what are you waiting for, boy?
拿着抹布 别在心里咒我
t the mop. And don't cuss at me.
好的
Okay.
告诉我 我们还在这里干吗？
So, what are we still doing here?
我不知道 我 我只是
l don't know. I just…
我只是有不好的感觉
l still have a bad feeling.
为什么？密苏里 已经把问题解决了
Why? Missouri did her Zelda Rubinstein thing.
这房子干净了 这该结束了
This should be over.
是的 应该这样
Yeah. Well, probably.
但我只是还想确认一下 就这样
But I just wanna make sure, that's all.
可我现在只想上床睡觉
Well, problem is, I could be sleeping in a bed right now.
迪恩 迪恩
Dean. Dean!
你去救孩子 我去救詹妮
You grab the kids, I'll get Jenny.
快呀
on.
詹妮
me on! Jenny!
我开不了门了
l can't open the door!
退后
Stand back.
来
Come on.
不 我的孩子
No, my kids!
萨姆去救你孩子了 快跟我走
m's got your kids. Come on.
救命
Help!
不要
Please.
来这 别看它 别看
Come here. Come here. Don't look. Don't look.
莎丽 带你弟弟快离开这里 别回头看
Sari, take your brother outside as fast as you can. Don't look back.
你没事吧 孩子？
Are you okay, baby?
莎丽 萨姆在哪里？
Sari, where's Sam?
他在里面 有东西抓住了他
He's inside. Something has got him.
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
萨姆
Sam!
萨姆 萨姆
sam? Sam.
不 不要 不要
No! Don't! Don't!
什么？为什么？
What? Why?
因为我知道她是谁了
Because I know who it is.
我现在看到她了
I can see her now.
妈妈
Mom?
迪恩
Dean.
萨姆
Sam.
对不起
I'm sorry.
对不起什么？
For what?
你 滚出我的家
You get out of my house.
放过我的孩子
And let go of my son.
妈妈
Mom?
现在都结束了
Now it's over.
谢谢
Thanks for these.
别谢谢我 本来就是你的
Don't thank me. They're yours.
这里再也没鬼魂了
Well, there are no spirits in there anymore.
这次确定了
This time for sure.
我妈妈也不在吗？
Not even my mom?
是的
No.
发生了什么？
What happened?
你妈妈的灵魂和那个灵魂
Your mom's spirit and the poltergeist's energy…
它们互相抵消了
they canceled each other out.
你妈妈用自己摧毁了那个东西
Your mom destroyed herself going after the thing.
她为什么要那么做？
Why would she do something like that?
当然是为了保护她的孩子
Well, to protect her boys, of course.
萨姆 我很难过
Sam, l'm sorry.
为什么？
For what?
你感觉到了你妈妈 不是吗？
You sensed it was here, didn't you?
而我却不能
Even when I couldn't.
我怎么了？
What's happening to me?
我知道我该有答案
I know I should have all the answers…
但我不知道
but I don't know.
萨姆 好了吗？
Sam, you ready?
- 再见 - 再见
- Bye. - Bye.
谢谢 萨姆
Thanks, Sam.
以后别当我是陌生人
Don't you boys be strangers.
不会的
We won't.
再见
See you around.
那个孩子
That boy.
他拥有那么强大的力量
I mean, he has such powerful abilities.
可他却为什么不能感觉到自己的爸爸
Why he couldn't sense his own father.
不知道为什么
I have no idea.
玛丽的灵魂
Mary's spirit?
你真的觉得是她救了孩子？
Do you really think she saved the boys?
是的
I do.
约翰·温彻斯特 我真想扁你一顿
John Winchester, I could just slap you.
你为什么不去和你孩子见面？
Why don't you go talk to your children?
天啊 我也想
I want to.
你不知道我有多想见他们
You have no idea how much I wanna see them.
但我不能 现在不行
but I can't. Not yet.
直到我发现真相时
Not until I know the truth.